Guide to the University of Chicago Department of History Records 1905-1990
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Administrative Materials
  - Subseries 4: Reports and Proposals
    - History, Triennial Report, Folder 2, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - History, Triennial Report, Folder 3, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - History, Triennial Report, Folder 4, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - History, Visiting Committee, Papers, Folder 1, 1970-1974 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - History, Visiting Committee, Papers, Folder 2, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - History, Visiting Committee, Papers, Folder 3, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - History, Visiting Committee, Papers, Folder 4, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - History, Visiting Committee, Papers, Folder 5, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - History, Visiting Committee, Papers, Folder 6, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - History, Visiting Committee, Papers, Folder 7, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - History, Visiting Committee, Papers, Folder 8, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - History, Visiting Committee, Papers, Folder 9, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - History, Social History Proposal, Workshop, Folder 1, 1971-1975 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - History, Committee on Women, Papers, 1971-1980 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - History, Committee on Women, Report, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - History, Social History, Workshop, Folder 2, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 5: Applications for Faculty Positions
    - Applications, Faculty Positions, Folder 1, 1914-1930 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Applications, Faculty Positions, Folder 2, 1931 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Applications, Faculty Positions, Folder 3, 1932-1933 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Applications, Faculty Positions, Folder 4, 1933-1934 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Applications, Faculty Positions, Folder 5, 1935-1937 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Applications, Faculty Positions, Folder 6, 1938-1939 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Applications, Faculty Positions, Folder 7, 1940-1946 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Applications, Faculty Positions, Folder 8, 1946-1948 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 6: Fishbein Center Materials
    - History, Fishbein Center, Report Response, 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - History, Fishbein Center, Brochures, 1968-1978 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - History, Fishbein Center, Lectures, Publicity, 1970-1977 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - History, Fishbein Center, Annual Reports, 1971-1975 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - History, Fishbein Center, Membership, 1971-1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - History, Fishbein Center, Memos, Folder 1, 1971-1977 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - History, Fishbein Center, Memos, Folder 2, 1972-1979 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - History, Fishbein Center, Students, 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - History, Fishbein Center, Fundraising, 1975-1977 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - History, Fishbein Center, History of Science, Papers, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 7: Library Administration Papers
    - University of Chicago, Library, Board, Papers, Folder 1, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - University of Chicago, Library, Board, Papers, Folder 2, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - University of Chicago, Library, Board, Papers, Folder 3, 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - University of Chicago, Library, Board, Papers, Folder 4, 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - University of Chicago, Library, Board, Papers, Folder 5, 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - University of Chicago, Library, Board, Papers, Folder 6, 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - University of Chicago, Library, Board, Papers, Folder 7, 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - History, Library Holdings, Survey, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 8: Miscellaneous Administrative Materials
    - History, Graduate Handbook, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - History, Bradburn, Norman, Papers, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - History, Cooperative College Registry, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - History, Cantor, Norman, Papers, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - History, Common Room, Papers, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - History, Course Numbering, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - History, Kruskal, Divisional Correspondence, 1974-1984 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - History, Vieira, David, Papers, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - History, S.S. Building, 50th Anniversary, Papers, 1975-1980 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - History, Kruskal, Social Sciences, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - History, Departmental Mailings, Folder 1, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - History, Departmental Mailings, Folder 2, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - History, Departmental Mailings, Folder 3, 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - History, Departmental Mailings, Folder 4, 1977-1980 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - History, The College Faculty, Newsletter, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - History, Bill, Shirley, and Charles, Papers, 1978-1983 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - History, December 15th Cases, 1979-1981 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - History, Honorary Degrees Committee, Folder 1, 1965-1977 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - History, Honorary Degrees Committee, Folder 2, 1976-1987 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - History, Honorary Degrees Committee, Folder 6, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - History, Newsletter Information, Correspondence, 1969-1978 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - History, Alumni Addresses, Xerox Label Masters, 1975-1987 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - History, Chicago Humanities Project, Humanistic Inquiry, 1971-1973 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - History, Indian History Teaching Prospects, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - History, Schaffner Professorship, Papers, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - History, Misc. Papers, 1972-1978 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Secretary of the Faculties, Papers, 1972-1979 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - History, Nieva, Constantino, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - History, Russian Civilization, Memos, 1973-1979 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - History, Islamic Search, Candidates, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - History, Salary Scale, University of California, Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - History, Social Philosophy, Levine, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - History, Lawrence Stone, Honorary Degree Materials, 1978-1980 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - History, Recruitment Brochure, Papers, 1978-1983 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - History, Social Sciences, Stocking, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - History, Fiftieth Anniversary Committee, Papers, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - History, Student Teaching, Papers, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Series III: Teaching Materials
  Series III contains unrestricted student records for M.A., Ph.D., and other students, records of fellowships and scholarships, student recommendation letters, copies of course examinations, course schedules, course reading lists, memos of work, and papers pertaining to student organizations and clubs. Series III is divided into six subseries.
  Subseries 1 contains unrestricted student records for M.A., Ph.D., and other students; subseries 2 contains papers pertaining to student fellowships and scholarships; subseries 3 contains recommendation letters; subseries 4 contains course examinations; subseries 5 contains other course and degree materials; and subseries 6 contains other miscellaneous academic materials.
  - Subseries 1: Student Records
    - History, Student Records, Other, Folder 1, 1930-1938 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - History, Student Records, Other, Folder 2, 1930-1938 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - History, Student Records, Other, Folder 3, 1930-1938 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - History, Student Records, M.A., Folder 1, 1927-1938 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - History, Student Records, M.A., Folder 2, 1927-1938 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - History, Student Records, M.A., Folder 3, 1927-1938 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - History, Student Records, M.A., Folder 4, 1927-1938 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - History, Student Records, M.A., Folder 5, 1927-1938 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - History, Student Records, M.A., Folder 6, 1927-1938 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - History, Student Records, M.A., Folder 7, 1927-1938 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - History, Student Records, M.A., Folder 8, 1927-1938 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - History, Student Records, M.A., Folder 9, 1927-1938 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - History, Student Records, PhD, Folder 1, 1927-1938 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - History, Student Records, PhD, Folder 2, 1927-1938 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - History, Student Records, PhD, Folder 3, 1927-1938 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - History, Student Records, PhD, Folder 4, 1927-1938 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - History, Student Records, PhD, Folder 5, 1927-1938 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - History, Student Records, PhD, Folder 6, 1927-1938 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - History, Student Records, PhD, Folder 7, 1927-1938 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - History, Student Records, PhD, Folder 8, 1927-1938 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - History, Student Records, PhD, Folder 9, 1927-1938 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - History, Student Records, PhD, Folder 10, 1927-1938 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - History, Student Records, PhD, Folder 11, 1927-1938 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 2: Fellowships and Scholarships
    - History, Graduate Schools, Report, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - History, Theory of Education, Report, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - History, Fellowships and Scholarships, Records, Folder 1, 1926-1931 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - History, Fellowships and Scholarships, Records, Folder 2, 1930-1938 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - History, Committee on History, Report, 1934 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - History, Smith Scholarships, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 3: Recommendation Letters
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 1, 1910-1915 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 2, 1916-1921 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 3, 1922-1923 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 4, 1924 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 5, 1925 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 6, 1926 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 7, 1927 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 8, 1928 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 9, 1929 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 10, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 11, 1931 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 12, 1932-1933 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 13, 1934 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 14, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 15, 1936 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 16, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 17, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 4: Examinations
    - History, Miscellaneous Exams, Folder 1, 1905-1914 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - History, Miscellaneous Exams, Folder 2, 1907-1912 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - History, MA/PhD Exams, Folder 1, 1927-1933 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - History, MA/PhD Exams, Folder 2, 1929-1934 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - History, Master’s Exams, Folder 1, 1928-1933 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - History, PhD Exams, Folder 1, 1928-1933 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - History, Course Exams, Folder 1, 1931-1947 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - History, A.B. Exams, Folder 1, 1934-1938 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - History, Comprehensive Examinations, Questions, Folder 1, 1934-1938 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - History, Comprehensive Examinations, Questions, Folder 2, 1934-1940 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - History, Comprehensive Examinations, Questions, Folder 3, 1936-1942 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - History, B.A. Exam, Abolishment, 1970-1973 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 5: Course and Degree Materials
    - Courses and Degrees, Memos of Work, Folder 1, 1924-1935 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Courses and Degrees, Memos of Work, Folder 2, 1924-1935 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Courses and Degrees, Memos of Work, Folder 3, 1924-1937 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Courses and Degrees, Memos of Work, Folder 4, 1925-1935 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Courses and Degrees, Memos of Work, Folder 5, 1927-1935 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Courses and Degrees, Memos of Work, Folder 6, 1927-1938 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Courses and Degrees, Memos of Work, Folder 7, 1927-1939 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Courses and Degrees, Course Schedules, 1928-1930 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Courses and Degrees, Social Science Courses, 1945-1946 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - History, Courses, McNeil, Social History, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - History, Course Offerings, Miscellaneous, Folder 1, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - History, Course Offerings, Miscellaneous, Folder 2, 1961-1962 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - History, Course Offerings, Miscellaneous, Folder 3, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - History, Course Offerings, Miscellaneous, Folder 4, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - History, Renaissance Seminar, Papers, Folder 1, 1971-1974 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - History, Renaissance Seminar, Papers, Folder 2, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - History, Course Number 300, Old Papers, 1972-1973 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - History, Courses, Craven, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - History, Courses, Wade, Urban History, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - History, Reading List, Expansion of Europe, Folder 1, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - History, Reading List, Expansion of Europe, Folder 2, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - History, Reading List, Expansion of Europe, Folder 3, undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - History, Reading List, Expansion of Europe, Folder 4, undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - History, Student Manual, 1915 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - History, B.A. Students, Record Cards, Folder 1, 1922-1938 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - History, B.A. Students, Record Cards, Folder 2, 1930-1938 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - History, Resident Faculty, Schedules, 1926-1933 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - History, Requirements for Degrees in History, Manual, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - History, Course Reading Lists, Folder 1, 1942-1945 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - History, Course Reading Lists, Folder 2, 1943-1948 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 6: Miscellaneous Academic Materials
    - History, Hutchinson, Department of History in Retrospect, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - History, Philosophy of Science Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - History, Dean Adams, Papers, 1968-1974 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - History, Special Materials Furnished by Historians, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - History, Departmental Documents, 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - History, Art History, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Adlai Stevenson Institute, Working paper I, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - History, 80th Anniversary, Inquiries, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - History, Divisional Advisory and Policy Committee, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - History, Ad-hoc Committee, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - History, Armenian Studies Program, 1973-1982 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - History, American Council of Learned Societies, Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - History, Oriental Institute, ACLU Commager Lecture, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - History, Advanced Placement, Papers, 1978-1982 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - History, AHA, Washington, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - History, History Club, Minutes, Folder 1, 1915-1922 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - History, History Club, Minutes, Folder 2, 1915-1922 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - History, Student Organizations, 1926-1927 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - History, Hutchinson, WM.T, Dept. of History in Retrospect, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - History, Library Resources, Bird, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - History, Ph.D. Hoods, Gift Tradition, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - History, Bidwell, Education, 1971-1973 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - History, CIC, History of Science Programs, Chicago Historians of Science, 1972-1974 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - History, Braude, Gideon Lowinsky, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - History, Fulbright-Hays, Papers, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - History, Banfield Visit, Freedom of Speech Concerns, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - History, Harris Motion, Papers, Folder 1, 1972-1975 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - History, Harris Motion, Papers, Folder 2, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - History, Harris Motion, Papers, Folder 3, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - History, Harris Motion, Papers, Folder 4, 1974-1976 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - History, Brown, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - History, Boorstin, Syllabi and lecture notes, circa 1960 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Series IV: Restricted
  Series IV contains restricted administrative, financial, and evaluative information. The series is divided into two subseries: Administrative Restrictions and Academic Restrictions.
  In Subseries 1, Folder 46 is restricted until 2023. Folders 47-49 are restricted for 50 years from date of creation (material is restricted until 2019-2040).
  In Subseries 2, Folders 50-58 are restricted for 80 years from date of creation (material is restricted until 2019-2064).
  The entire series will be available in 2064.
  - Subseries 1: Administrative Restrictions
    - Council of the University Senate, Minutes, Folder 1, 1976-1981 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Council of the University Senate, Minutes, Folder 2, 1978-1979 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Council of the University Senate, Minutes, Folder 3, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Council of the University Senate, Minutes, Folder 4, 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Council of the University Senate, Minutes, Folder 5, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Council of the University Senate, Minutes, Folder 6, 1982-1990 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - History, Subcommittee Meetings and Recommendations, Folder 1, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - History, Subcommittee Meetings and Recommendations, Folder 2, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - History, Committee on African Studies, 1970-1981 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - History, Aid and Admissions, Folder 1, 1970-1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - History, Aid and Admissions, Folder 2, 1970-1974 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - History, Aid and Admissions, Folder 3, 1973-1980 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - History, Aid and Admissions, Folder 4, 1975-1979 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - History, Aid and Admissions, Folder 5, 1975-1982 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - History, Aid and Admissions, Folder 6, 1980-1982 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - History, Latin American, Appointment Prospects, Folder 1, 1969-1972 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - History, Latin American, Appointment Prospects, Folder 2, 1969-1972 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - History, Latin American, Appointment Prospects, Folder 3, 1970-1972 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - History, Latin American, Appointment Prospects, Folder 4, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - History, Reappointment and Promotions Committee, Folder 1, 1970-1973 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - History, Reappointment and Promotions Committee, Folder 2, 1970-1973 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - History, Honorary Degrees Committee, Folder 3, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - History, Honorary Degrees Committee, Folder 4, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - History, Honorary Degrees Committee, Folder 5, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - History, Fishbein Center, Search Committee, 1973-1977 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - History, Allen Debus, Morris Fishbein Professor, Nomination, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - History, Search Committee, Modern European Search, Folder 1, 1968-1972 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - History, Search Committee, Modern European Search, Folder 2, 1969-1974 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - History, Search Committee, Modern European Search, Folder 3, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - History, Tenure Cases, Committee Reports, Folder 1, 1969-1977 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - History, Tenure Cases, Committee Reports, Folder 2, 1970-1976 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - History, Assistant Professorship, Appointment, 1970-1971 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - History, Faculty, Reviews, 1970-1976 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - University of Chicago, Library, Search Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - History, Committee on Women, Folder 1, 1971-1980 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - History, Vallianatos, E.G., Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - History, Search Committee, Papers, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - History, Russian History, J. Brooks, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - History, Faculty Staffing, Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 2: Academic Restrictions
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 18, 1939 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 19, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 20, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 21, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 22, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 23, 1942 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 24, 1943 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 25, 1944 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 26, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 27, 1946 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 28, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Student Recommendations, Letters, Folder 29, 1948 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - History, Exam Evaluations, Folder 1, 1932-1945 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - History, Exam Evaluations, Folder 2, 1934-1946 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - History, A.B. Exams, Folder 2, 1939-1947 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Examination Charts, Folder 1, 1948-1949 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Examination Charts, Folder 2, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - History, Qualifying Exams, Folder 1, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - History, Qualifying Exams, Folder 2, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - History, MA/PhD Exams, Folder 3, 1934-1943 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - History, MA/PhD Exams, Folder 4, 1944-1948 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - History, Fellowships, Records and Evaluations, Folder 1, 1939-1942 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - History, Fellowships, Records and Evaluations, Folder 2, 1942-1944 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - History, Fellowships, Records and Evaluations, Folder 3, 1944-1948 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - History, Fellowships, Records and Evaluations, Folder 4, 1944-1947 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - History, Graduate Students, Lists, 1940-1948 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Alden-Caspari, 1934-1957 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Cate, J.L., 1937-1957 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Chads-Crane, 1929-1957 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Craven, A.O., 1929-1955 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Creel-Ganshof, 1931-1957 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Gillespie, F.E., 1930-1948 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Gottschalk, L.R., Folder 1, 1930-1939 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Gottschalk, L.R., Folder 2, 1939-1957 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Greene-Halperin, 1943-1957 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Handlin-Hotchkiss, 1924-1956 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Hutchinson, W.T., Folder 1, 1934-1947 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Hutchinson, W.T., Folder 2, 1948-1957 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Huth-Jernegan, 1933-1951 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Johnson, T.W., Folder 1, 1940-1950 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Johnson, T.W., Folder 2, 1950-1954 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Johnson, T.W., Folder 3, 1954-1957 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - History, Instructors’ Reports, Joranson, E., Folder 1, 1930-1937 (Box 54, Folder 5)